<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Cheapest websites on the internet | websites.powered-by.love</title>
    <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love" />
    <updated>2023-08-04T11:09:01+04:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://websites.powered-by.love</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Amzing advantages of static websites</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/advantages-of-static-websites/"/>
        <id>https://websites.powered-by.love/advantages-of-static-websites/</id>
            <category term="blog"/>

        <updated>2023-08-03T09:07:15+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Introduction: In the world of web development, the allure of flashy animations and dynamic content can sometimes overshadow the true essence of a website: delivering valuable information efficiently and effectively. While dynamic websites have their place, static websites offer a wealth of advantages that businesses&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/2023-08-03_09-05-2.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/responsive/2023-08-03_09-05-2-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/responsive/2023-08-03_09-05-2-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/responsive/2023-08-03_09-05-2-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/responsive/2023-08-03_09-05-2-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/responsive/2023-08-03_09-05-2-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/21/responsive/2023-08-03_09-05-2-2xl.png 1600w"  height="924" width="1524" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    Introduction:<br><br>In the world of web development, the allure of flashy animations and dynamic content can sometimes overshadow the true essence of a website: delivering valuable information efficiently and effectively. While dynamic websites have their place, static websites offer a wealth of advantages that businesses and individuals should not overlook. In this blog post, we will explore the numerous benefits of embracing the simplicity and elegance of a static website.<br><br>    Blazing Fast Load Times:<br><br>One of the most significant advantages of static websites is their lightning-fast load times. Unlike dynamic websites that require server-side processing for each page request, static websites serve pre-rendered HTML files directly to visitors. This speed not only improves user experience but also positively impacts search engine rankings and conversion rates.<br><br>    Enhanced Security:<br><br>Static websites are inherently more secure than their dynamic counterparts. With no backend scripts or databases to exploit, the attack surface is significantly reduced. By reducing the risk of security breaches, static websites provide peace of mind to both website owners and visitors.<br><br>    Cost-Effectiveness:<br><br>Hosting and maintaining a static website is considerably more cost-effective than managing a dynamic one. Since static sites don't require complex server configurations or databases, the hosting expenses are significantly lower. Additionally, fewer server resources are needed, resulting in reduced hosting fees.<br><br>    High Reliability and Availability:<br><br>Since static websites do not rely on server-side processing, they are less prone to server failures or downtime. This inherent stability ensures that your website remains accessible to visitors, enhancing your online reputation and preventing potential business disruptions.<br><br>    Improved SEO Performance:<br><br>Static websites tend to perform exceptionally well in search engine rankings. Faster load times and cleaner code contribute to a better user experience, leading to higher search engine visibility. Additionally, static websites often have simpler URLs, making them more search engine-friendly.<br><br>    Easy Version Control and Maintenance:<br><br>With static websites, version control and maintenance become a breeze. You can track changes efficiently using version control systems like Git, allowing you to roll back to previous versions if needed. This simplicity makes it easier to collaborate with teams and implement updates seamlessly.<br><br>    Scalability:<br><br>Static websites can handle a high volume of traffic without straining server resources. By leveraging Content Delivery Networks (CDNs), you can distribute your website's assets across multiple servers globally, ensuring optimal performance for visitors from any location.<br><br>Conclusion:<br><br>In a world where complexity often prevails, static websites stand out as a beacon of simplicity and elegance. With their unparalleled speed, security, and cost-effectiveness, static websites offer a compelling case for businesses and individuals seeking an efficient online presence. Embracing the advantages of a static website not only enhances user experience but also allows you to focus on delivering valuable content without being bogged down by unnecessary complexities. So, don't underestimate the power of simplicity—consider a static website and unlock its full potential for your online endeavors.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Social Media Alone Isn&#x27;t Enough</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/why-social-media-alone-isnt-enough-for-your-business/"/>
        <id>https://websites.powered-by.love/why-social-media-alone-isnt-enough-for-your-business/</id>
            <category term="blog"/>

        <updated>2023-08-03T09:03:25+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Introduction: In the digital age, social media has become an integral part of our lives, connecting people and businesses on a global scale. While having a strong social media presence is undeniably valuable, it's important to recognize that relying solely on social media is not&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/2023-08-03_09-02.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/responsive/2023-08-03_09-02-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/responsive/2023-08-03_09-02-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/responsive/2023-08-03_09-02-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/responsive/2023-08-03_09-02-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/responsive/2023-08-03_09-02-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/20/responsive/2023-08-03_09-02-2xl.png 1600w"  height="846" width="1537" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    Introduction:<br><br>In the digital age, social media has become an integral part of our lives, connecting people and businesses on a global scale. While having a strong social media presence is undeniably valuable, it's important to recognize that relying solely on social media is not enough to sustain and grow a business. In this blog post, we will explore the reasons why having a dedicated website is essential and how directing all your traffic to your website can lead to more significant benefits for your business.<br><br>    Control and Ownership:<br><br>One of the most critical advantages of having a website is that you have complete control and ownership over your online presence. Social media platforms can change algorithms, policies, or even shut down, potentially leaving your business in the dark. Having a website allows you to maintain a consistent brand image and messaging, free from the limitations imposed by third-party platforms.<br><br>    Credibility and Professionalism:<br><br>A website lends credibility and professionalism to your business. It serves as a digital storefront that showcases your products, services, and company values in a comprehensive and organized manner. This professional image can instill trust in potential customers, encouraging them to engage further with your business.<br><br>    Customization and Flexibility:<br><br>A website provides the freedom to design a unique and personalized experience for your visitors. You can tailor the layout, content, and user experience to align with your brand identity and target audience. Unlike social media, which operates within predefined templates and constraints, a website gives you the flexibility to create a memorable and immersive online environment.<br><br>    Enhanced Branding and Storytelling:<br><br>A website is an ideal platform for storytelling and strengthening your brand narrative. Through captivating visuals, compelling storytelling, and engaging content, you can forge emotional connections with your audience, fostering long-term relationships that extend beyond social media platforms.<br><br>    Search Engine Visibility:<br><br>Having a website with well-optimized content improves your visibility on search engines like Google. When users search for products or services related to your business, a website can attract organic traffic, further expanding your reach and potential customer base.<br><br>    Data and Analytics:<br><br>A website equipped with analytics tools provides valuable insights into your audience's behavior, preferences, and interests. This data-driven approach empowers you to make informed decisions, refine marketing strategies, and tailor your offerings to better meet customer needs.<br><br>    Conversion and Sales:<br><br>While social media can drive awareness and engagement, a website is a more effective platform for converting leads into customers. By guiding visitors through a seamless sales funnel and offering clear calls-to-action, you can increase conversion rates and boost your bottom line.<br><br>Conclusion:<br><br>In today's competitive digital landscape, relying solely on social media is akin to building a house on rented land. While social media platforms are undoubtedly valuable tools for brand visibility and engagement, a dedicated website serves as the solid foundation of your online presence. With control, credibility, customization, and data insights at your disposal, a website offers unparalleled opportunities for growth and success. By directing all your traffic to your website, you ensure that your business stands on its own, empowered to navigate the ever-changing digital landscape with confidence and resilience. So, invest in your website today and harness the true potential of your business in the digital realm.
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Importance of Having a Website</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/the-importance-of-having-a-website-for-your-small-business/"/>
        <id>https://websites.powered-by.love/the-importance-of-having-a-website-for-your-small-business/</id>
            <category term="blog"/>

        <updated>2023-08-03T09:00:51+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Introduction: In today's digital age, the significance of an online presence cannot be overstated. For small businesses, having a website has evolved from being an optional luxury to an absolute necessity. With the internet becoming the primary source of information for consumers, a well-designed website&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/2023-08-03_08-58.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/responsive/2023-08-03_08-58-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/responsive/2023-08-03_08-58-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/responsive/2023-08-03_08-58-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/responsive/2023-08-03_08-58-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/responsive/2023-08-03_08-58-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/19/responsive/2023-08-03_08-58-2xl.png 1600w"  height="1150" width="1875" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    Introduction:<br><br>In today's digital age, the significance of an online presence cannot be overstated. For small businesses, having a website has evolved from being an optional luxury to an absolute necessity. With the internet becoming the primary source of information for consumers, a well-designed website is a potent tool that can set small businesses apart from the competition and open doors to new opportunities. In this blog post, we will explore the compelling reasons why every small business should embrace the idea of having a website.<br><br>    Establish Credibility and Trust:<br><br>A professionally designed website can establish instant credibility and trust with potential customers. When consumers search for products or services online, a business without a website might seem outdated or untrustworthy. A website serves as a digital storefront that showcases the business's values, expertise, and commitment to providing top-notch services.<br><br>    Reach a Wider Audience:<br><br>Gone are the days when businesses relied solely on local foot traffic for success. With a website, a small business can reach a global audience and tap into new markets beyond their geographical boundaries. This expanded reach can significantly enhance growth prospects and revenue potential.<br><br>    Showcase Products and Services:<br><br>A website provides an ideal platform to showcase products and services in detail. Through high-quality images, engaging descriptions, and customer testimonials, small businesses can effectively communicate their unique value propositions and stand out in a crowded marketplace.<br><br>    Cost-Effective Marketing:<br><br>Compared to traditional advertising methods, a website offers a cost-effective marketing solution. It allows small businesses to promote their offerings 24/7, reaching potential customers at any time of day, without incurring significant expenses.<br><br>    Improve Customer Support:<br><br>A website can serve as a centralized hub for customer support. Small businesses can provide answers to frequently asked questions, offer downloadable guides, and maintain a blog to share valuable insights, thus empowering customers and building stronger relationships.<br><br>    Gather Customer Data and Insights:<br><br>By integrating analytics tools into their website, small businesses can gather valuable data about customer behavior, preferences, and demographics. These insights can be used to refine marketing strategies, tailor offerings to meet customer needs, and make data-driven decisions.<br><br>    Enhance Competitive Advantage:<br><br>In today's competitive landscape, having a website can be a game-changer. Businesses without an online presence may be losing potential customers to competitors who have embraced the digital realm. A well-optimized website can help level the playing field and provide a competitive advantage.<br><br>Conclusion:<br><br>In conclusion, the modern business landscape demands that small businesses adapt to the digital era. A website is not just a mere accessory; it's a powerful tool that can significantly impact a small business's success and growth. From building credibility to expanding reach, the benefits of having a website are too crucial to be ignored. Embracing an online presence is not only a smart business move but an indispensable one for small businesses looking to thrive in today's interconnected world. So, what are you waiting for? Take that step forward and set your small business on a path to digital success!
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Request Your Website</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/contact/"/>
        <id>https://websites.powered-by.love/contact/</id>

        <updated>2023-08-04T11:09:01+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    You can check your domain name availability here or we can do it together. Please fill in the form for details for the request. Our sales manager will&nbsp; contact you as soon as possible.❤️ Loading…
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/18/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2xl.png 1600w"  height="718" width="1880" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

    <h2 id="you-can-check-your-domain-name-availability">
      You can check your domain name availability
    </h2>

    <h1 id="here">
      <a href="https://name.am/" target="_blank">
      here
      </a>
    </h1>

    <h2 id="or-we-can-do-it-together">
      or we can do it together.
    </h2>

    <h1 id="please-fill-in-the-form-for-details-for-the-request-our-sales-manager-willnbsp-contact-you-as-soon-as-possible">
      Please fill in the form for details for the request. Our sales manager will&nbsp; contact you as soon as possible.❤️
    </h1>
<div><div class="my-iframe-container">
  <div class="post__iframe"><iframe loading="lazy" src="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeOkxnNLV16YdUNaA1BHU501mAII5bTra61YCktQjyPkAqVpQ/viewform?embedded=true" width="640" height="1500" frameborder="0" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0">Loading…</iframe></div>
</div></div>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>FAQ</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/faq/"/>
        <id>https://websites.powered-by.love/faq/</id>

        <updated>2023-08-04T09:52:21+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    How is hosting free? We use free tools like Publii, Github pages to make your website most affordable! Also our websites are powered by love. ❤️ How many revisions will I have? We will provide 3 revisions to fix any content issues. Later we will&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2xl.png 1600w"  height="718" width="1880" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

    <h1 id="how-is-hosting-free">
      How is hosting free?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="we-use-free-tools-like-publii-github-pages-to-make-your-website-most-affordable-also-our-websites-are-powered-by-love-">
      We use free tools like Publii, Github pages to make your website most affordable! Also our websites are powered by love. ❤️
    </h3>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/rect234-2.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/rect234-2-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/rect234-2-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/rect234-2-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/rect234-2-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/rect234-2-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/17/responsive/rect234-2-2xl.png 1600w"  height="193" width="1000" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

    <h1 id="how-many-revisions-will-i-have">
      How many revisions will I have?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="we-will-provide-3-revisions-to-fix-any-content-issues-later-we-will-provide-a-package-with-instruction-on-how-to-add-your-own-content-to-your-website-additional-changes-can-be-provided-on-a-contract-basesbr">
      We will provide 3 revisions to fix any content issues. Later we will provide a package with instruction on how to add your own content to your website. Additional changes can be provided on a contract bases!<br>
    </h3>

    <h1 id="do-you-include-com-domain">
      Do you include .COM domain?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="yes-com-domain-is-included-first-year-for-free-next-year-domain-will-cost-only-19usd-a-yearbr">
      Yes, .COM domain is included first year for free. Next year domain will cost only 19USD a year.<br>
    </h3>

    <h1 id="is-it-secure">
      Is it secure?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="ask-any-professional-span-stylefontweight-normalstatic-websitesspan-are-one-of-the-most-secure-types-of-website">
      Ask any professional, <span style="font-weight: normal;">static websites</span> are one of the most secure types of website.
    </h3>

    <h1 id="what-is-difference-between-a-landing-page-vs-website">
      What is difference between a landing page vs website?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="a-website-is-a-collection-of-interconnected-web-pages-with-diverse-content-and-purposes-while-a-landing-page-is-a-single-focused-page-designed-to-drive-a-specific-action-or-conversion">
      A website is a collection of interconnected web pages with diverse content and purposes, while a landing page is a single, focused page designed to drive a specific action or conversion.
    </h3>

    <h1 id="how-many-themes-do-you-offer">
      How many themes do you offer?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="as-we-are-focused-on-speed-and-performance-at-the-moment-there-is-just-one-theme-we-plan-to-offer-new-themes-going-forward">
      As we are focused on speed and performance at the moment there is just one theme. We plan to offer new themes going forward.
    </h3>

    <h1 id="do-you-support-any-languages-other-than-english">
      Do you support any languages other than English?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="at-the-moment-its-only-english">
      At the moment it's only English.
    </h3>

    <h1 id="can-i-request-additional-features">
      Can I request additional features?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="right-now-we-offer-minimal-customisation-but-we-are-working-hard-to-become-more-flexible">
      Right now we offer minimal customisation, but we are working hard to become more flexible.
    </h3>

    <h1 id="who-suites-this-platform-best">
      Who suites this platform best?
    </h1>

    <h3 id="this-platform-is-for-any-business-and-individual-you-may-find-some-of-them-in-the-list-below">
      This platform is for any business and individual, you may find some of them in the list below.
    </h3>

  <p>
    Small businesses / Startups / Non-profit organizations / Restaurants and cafes / Retail stores / Freelancers and consultants / Photographers and artists / Personal blogs or portfolios / Event planners and organizers / Real estate agents / Educational institutions (schools, tutoring centers, etc.) / Health and wellness professionals / Travel agencies or tour operators / Legal firms and attorneys / Accounting and financial services / Construction and home improvement companies / Sports clubs and teams / Pet services and businesses Wedding planners and services / Entertainment and media companies / Fashion designers and boutiques / Interior designers and home decor businesses / Music bands and musicians / Fitness and gym facilities / Automotive and car-related businesses / Beauty salons and spas / Healthcare providers (doctors, dentists, clinics) / Environmental and sustainability organizations / Marketing and advertising agencies / Coaching and personal development services / Handmade and craft businesses / Food and catering services / Online courses and educational platforms / Religious organizations and places of worship / Agricultural and farming businesses / Gaming and entertainment websites / Parenting and family-oriented websites / Green energy and renewable technology companies
  </p>

    <h1 id="request-your-website-">
      <a href="https://websites.powered-by.love/contact/">
      Request Your Website 🪄
      </a>
    </h1>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>We make internet affordable.</title>
        <author>
            <name>Arevik Aroyan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://websites.powered-by.love/home/"/>
        <id>https://websites.powered-by.love/home/</id>

        <updated>2023-08-04T09:54:32+04:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    One time payment .COM website/landing page only&nbsp; for 119 USD. Pay only 19 USD for your domain name next year.&nbsp;Hosting FREE forever, no hidden fees!&nbsp; Request Your Website&nbsp;🪄 Ideal solution for a small business. 1 theme 1 choose, no difficult decisions! Mobile and Desktop optimized/responsive&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                
    <h1 id="span-stylefontweight-normalone-time-payment-spancomspan-stylefontweight-normal-websitelanding-page-onlynbsp-for-span119-usdspan-stylefontweight-normalspanbr">
      <span style="font-weight: normal;">One time payment </span>.COM<span style="font-weight: normal;"> website/landing page only&nbsp; for </span>119 USD<span style="font-weight: normal;">.</span><br>
    </h1>

    <h2 id="span-stylefontweight-normalpay-only-19-usd-for-your-domain-name-next-yearnbsphosting-spanfree-foreverspan-stylefontweight-normal-no-hidden-feesnbspspanbr">
      <span style="font-weight: normal;">Pay only 19 USD for your domain name next year.&nbsp;Hosting </span>FREE forever<span style="font-weight: normal;">, no hidden fees!&nbsp;</span><br>
    </h2>

    <h1 id="request-your-websitespan-stylefontweight-normalnbspspan">
      <a href="https://websites.powered-by.love/contact/">
      Request Your Website<span style="font-weight: normal;">&nbsp;🪄</span>
      </a>
    </h1>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/removal.ai_214b4157-aac8-4cd3-b562-860cccdc4b7f-2023-08-03_08-09-2-2xl.png 1600w"  height="718" width="1880" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

    <h3 id="ideal-solution-for-a-small-business">
      Ideal solution for a small business.
    </h3>
<hr class="separator separator--long-line" />

    <h3 id="span-stylefontweight-normal1-theme-1-spanspan-stylefontweight-400choosespanspan-stylefontweight-normal-spanno-difficult-decisions">
      <span style="font-weight: normal;">1 theme 1 </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">choose</span><span style="font-weight: normal;">, </span>no difficult decisions!
    </h3>
<div id="example-can-be-seen-at-arevikaroyancom"><h3>Mobile and Desktop optimized/responsive</h3>
<h3>Example can be seen at <a target="_blank" href="https://arevikaroyan.com">arevikaroyan.com</a></h3></div>

  <div  class="gallery-wrapper">
    <div class="gallery" data-columns="2">
      <figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/gallery/2023-08-03_09-31.png" data-size="440x797">
        <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/gallery/2023-08-03_09-31-thumbnail.png" height="797" width="440" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure><figure class="gallery__item">
      <a href="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/gallery/2023-08-03_09-30.png" data-size="2256x1356">
        <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/gallery/2023-08-03_09-30-thumbnail.png" height="769" width="1280" alt="" />
      </a>
      
    </figure>
    </div>
  </div>

    <h3 id="secure-free-https-enabledbrstatic-website-for-enhanced-securitybr">
      Secure! Free HTTPS enabled.<br>Static website for enhanced security.<br>
    </h3>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/rect2d34.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect2d34-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect2d34-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect2d34-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect2d34-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect2d34-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect2d34-2xl.png 1600w"  height="179" width="1000" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

    <h3 id="search-engine-optimised-website-will-be-registered-in-google-console-for-better-search-results">
      Search engine optimised. Website will be registered in Google Console for better search results.
    </h3>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/rect234-2.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect234-2-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect234-2-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect234-2-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect234-2-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect234-2-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/rect234-2-2xl.png 1600w"  height="193" width="1000" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

    <h3 id="google-analytics-embedded-user-video-interaction-recordings-withnbspposthog">
      Google analytics embedded, user video interaction recordings with&nbsp;Posthog.
    </h3>

    <figure class="post__image post__image--center">
      <img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/2023-08-03_07-14.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/2023-08-03_07-14-xs.png 300w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/2023-08-03_07-14-sm.png 480w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/2023-08-03_07-14-md.png 768w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/2023-08-03_07-14-lg.png 1024w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/2023-08-03_07-14-xl.png 1360w ,https://websites.powered-by.love/media/posts/16/responsive/2023-08-03_07-14-2xl.png 1600w"  height="1301" width="2142" alt="" />
      
    </figure>

  <p>
    
  </p>
<hr class="separator separator--dots" />

    <h3 id="brrequest-your-website-">
      <a href="https://websites.powered-by.love/contact/">
      <br>Request Your Website 🪄
      </a>
    </h3>

    <h3 id="read-faq-for-more-information">
      <a href="https://websites.powered-by.love/faq/">
      Read FAQ for more information
      </a>
    </h3>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
